<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title></title>
 <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="/"/>
 <updated>2014-02-20T12:23:41-05:00</updated>
 <id></id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Scheduled</title>
   <link href="/tests/2020/01/01/1400-scheduled/"/>
   <updated>2020-01-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2020/01/01/1400-scheduled</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This post is scheduled to be published in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should not be displayed by the theme.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hello Again</title>
   <link href="/tests/2013/06/16/hello-again/"/>
   <updated>2013-06-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2013/06/16/hello-again</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is the end of the thing. Nor did such soothing scenes, however temporary, fail of at least as temporary an effect on Ahab. But if these secret golden keys did seem to open in him his own secret golden treasuries, yet did his breath upon them prove but tarnishing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, grassy glades! oh, ever vernal endless landscapes in the soul; in ye,—though long parched by the dead drought of the earthy life,—in ye, men yet may roll, like young horses in new morning clover; and for some few fleeting moments, feel the cool dew of the life immortal on them. Would to God these blessed calms would last. But the mingled, mingling threads of life are woven by warp and woof: calms crossed by storms, a storm for every calm. There is no steady unretracing progress in this life; we do not advance through fixed gradations, and at the last one pause:—through infancy&amp;#39;s unconscious spell, boyhood&amp;#39;s thoughtless faith, adolescence&amp;#39; doubt (the common doom), then scepticism, then disbelief, resting at last in manhood&amp;#39;s pondering repose of If. But once gone through, we trace the round again; and are infants, boys, and men, and Ifs eternally. Where lies the final harbor, whence we unmoor no more? In what rapt ether sails the world, of which the weariest will never weary? Where is the foundling&amp;#39;s father hidden? Our souls are like those orphans whose unwedded mothers die in bearing them: the secret of our paternity lies in their grave, and we must there to learn it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that same day, too, gazing far down from his boat&amp;#39;s side into that same golden sea, Starbuck lowly murmured:—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Loveliness unfathomable, as ever lover saw in his young bride&amp;#39;s eye!—Tell me not of thy teeth-tiered sharks, and thy kidnapping cannibal ways. Let faith oust fact; let fancy oust memory; I look deep down and do believe.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Stubb, fish-like, with sparkling scales, leaped up in that same golden light:—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I am Stubb, and Stubb has his history; but here Stubb takes oaths that he has always been jolly!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And jolly enough were the sights and the sounds that came bearing down before the wind, some few weeks after Ahab&amp;#39;s harpoon had been welded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a Nantucket ship, the Bachelor, which had just wedged in her last cask of oil, and bolted down her bursting hatches; and now, in glad holiday apparel, was joyously, though somewhat vain-gloriously, sailing round among the widely-separated ships on the ground, previous to pointing her prow for home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The three men at her mast-head wore long streamers of narrow red bunting at their hats; from the stern, a whale-boat was suspended, bottom down; and hanging captive from the bowsprit was seen the long lower jaw of the last whale they had slain. Signals, ensigns, and jacks of all colours were flying from her rigging, on every side. Sideways lashed in each of her three basketed tops were two barrels of sperm; above which, in her top-mast cross-trees, you saw slender breakers of the same precious fluid; and nailed to her main truck was a brazen lamp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As was afterwards learned, the Bachelor had met with the most surprising success; all the more wonderful, for that while cruising in the same seas numerous other vessels had gone entire months without securing a single fish. Not only had barrels of beef and bread been given away to make room for the far more valuable sperm, but additional supplemental casks had been bartered for, from the ships she had met; and these were stowed along the deck, and in the captain&amp;#39;s and officers&amp;#39; state-rooms. Even the cabin table itself had been knocked into kindling-wood; and the cabin mess dined off the broad head of an oil-butt, lashed down to the floor for a centrepiece. In the forecastle, the sailors had actually caulked and pitched their chests, and filled them; it was humorously added, that the cook had clapped a head on his largest boiler, and filled it; that the steward had plugged his spare coffee-pot and filled it; that the harpooneers had headed the sockets of their irons and filled them; that indeed everything was filled with sperm, except the captain&amp;#39;s pantaloons pockets, and those he reserved to thrust his hands into, in self-complacent testimony of his entire satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Another Post</title>
   <link href="/tests/2013/06/10/another-post/"/>
   <updated>2013-06-10T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2013/06/10/another-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As co-chairs of the House Sovereignty Caucus, we are concerned about the impact the U.N. Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities (Disabilities Treaty) will have on U.S. sovereignty and freedom. Reports have been circulating that the U.S. Senate plans to consider the Disabilities Treaty in early November even though it was defeated in the 112th Congress. We believe that joining the treaty will not enhance the rights of Americans with disabilities nor advance U.S. national interests abroad. Instead, the treaty’s vague definitions of “disability” and “sexual and reproductive health” invite abuse and the furtherance of abortion as a right, and Article 7 threatens Americans’ parental rights. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Disabilities Treaty establishes a body of unaccountable experts, the Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities, which evaluates the compliance of state parties to the treaty every four years, and issues recommendations for how they might improve in fulfilling their obligations. We are concerned that joining the treaty will allow foreign experts to interfere with U.S. policymaking and violate the principles of U.S. sovereignty. Too often U.N. treaty bodies seek to broaden the scope of the treaties that created them through treaty monitoring bodies, which expand language in original agreements and disregard national sovereignty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we find the language in the treaty especially concerning because it lacks concise definitions of very important terms. For example, the Disabilities Treaty lacks a clear definition of “disability,” which it defines as an evolving concept. This ambiguity invites abuse by persons or groups that do not suffer from a recognized medical disability but seek resources and protection under the authority of the treaty. This could also result in complicating the implementation of the treaty in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the treaty’s main purpose seeks to ensure the rights and protections of the disabled, the Disabilities Treaty includes the issue of sexual and reproductive health, which some U.N. staff has interpreted as “abortion rights.” While the nations who negotiated the treaty expressly rejected that interpretation, there is reason to believe the treaty monitoring body will read a right to abortion into the treaty like other treaty monitoring bodies have done for treaties that do not even include the controversial phrase. Abortion advocates and U.N. staff have already pointed to the Disabilities Treaty as a means to further build their case in favor of abortion as a human right. We strongly oppose this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are also concerned that Article 7 of the treaty would give the federal government the ability to override the decisions of parents of disabled children if the government believes its views are in the best interest of the child. This could strip parents of fundamental rights, including the ability to home school their children with disabilities if they believe it is in the best interests of their child. We support the rights of the disabled within the U.S., and the U.S. already holds itself to a high standard of human rights. We believe that the rights of Americans with disabilities are well protected under existing law and are enforced by a range of state and federal agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any modification or expansion of protections to Americans with disabilities should be achieved through the legislative process – not through an international treaty. Allowing an international panel of disability experts to scrutinize the U.S. record every four years could result in many unintended consequences for U.S. interests, yielding little or no benefit in realizing disability rights for Americans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, we believe that U.S. ratification of the Disabilities Treaty would not advance U.S. national interests abroad or the rights of Americans with disabilities here at home. This treaty would subject the U.S. to further intrusion by U.N. officials into policies that are sensitive domestic and social issues, and we remain convinced that the risks to the U.S. posed by this treaty far outweigh any potential benefits that could be realized by U.S. ratification.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hello World</title>
   <link href="/tests/2013/05/09/hello-world/"/>
   <updated>2013-05-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2013/05/09/hello-world</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Proin at eros non eros adipiscing mollis. Donec semper turpis sed diam. Sed consequat ligula nec tortor. Integer eget sem. Ut vitae enim eu est vehicula gravida. Morbi ipsum ipsum, porta nec, tempor id, auctor vitae, purus. Pellentesque neque. Nulla luctus erat vitae libero. Integer nec enim. Phasellus aliquam enim et tortor. Quisque aliquet, quam elementum condimentum feugiat, tellus odio consectetuer wisi, vel nonummy sem neque in elit. Curabitur eleifend wisi iaculis ipsum. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. In non velit non ligula laoreet ultrices. Praesent ultricies facilisis nisl. Vivamus luctus elit sit amet mi. Phasellus pellentesque, erat eget elementum volutpat, dolor nisl porta neque, vitae sodales ipsum nibh in ligula. Maecenas mattis pulvinar diam. Curabitur sed leo.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Page Image Alignment</title>
   <link href="/tests/2013/03/15/1919-page-image-alignment/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2013/03/15/1919-page-image-alignment</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to image alignment! The best way to demonstrate the ebb and flow of the various image positioning options is to nestle them snuggly among an ocean of words. Grab a paddle and let&amp;#39;s get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the topic of alignment, it should be noted that users can choose from the options ofÂ &lt;em&gt;None&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Left&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Right, &lt;/em&gt;andÂ &lt;em&gt;Center&lt;/em&gt;. In addition, they also get the options ofÂ &lt;em&gt;Thumbnail&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Medium&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Large&lt;/em&gt;Â &amp;amp;Â &lt;em&gt;Fullsize&lt;/em&gt;.
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-906 aligncenter&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg&quot; width=&quot;580&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
The image above happens to beÂ &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;centered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-904 alignleft&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The rest of this paragraph is fillerÂ for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150x150 image, which is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left aligned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.Â &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;As you can see the should be some space above&amp;quot;, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one moreÂ sentenceÂ here, we&amp;#39;ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image inÂ seamlessÂ transition. Again, letting the do it&amp;#39;s thang.Â Mission accomplished!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now for a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;massively large image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. It also has &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;alignnone  wp-image-907&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-905 alignright&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now we&amp;#39;re going to shift things to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;right align&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there... Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don&amp;#39;t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don&amp;#39;t let anyone else tell you differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty.Â Yeah... Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And just when you thought we were done, we&amp;#39;re going to do them all over again with captions!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_906&amp;quot; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;580&amp;quot;]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-906  &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg&quot; width=&quot;580&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt; Look at 580x300 getting some &lt;a title=&quot;Image Settings&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/images/image-settings/&quot;&gt;caption&lt;/a&gt; love.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above happens to beÂ &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;centered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. The caption also has a link in it, just to see if it does anything funky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_904&amp;quot; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;150&amp;quot;]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-904  &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt; Itty-bitty caption.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The rest of this paragraph is fillerÂ for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150x150 image, which is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left aligned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.Â &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one moreÂ sentenceÂ here, we&amp;#39;ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image inÂ seamlessÂ transition. Again, letting the do it&amp;#39;s thang. Mission accomplished!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now for a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;massively large image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. It also has &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_907&amp;quot; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;1200&amp;quot;]&lt;img class=&quot; wp-image-907&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt; Massive image comment for your eyeballs.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_905&amp;quot; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;quot;]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-905 &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt; Feels good to be right all the time.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now we&amp;#39;re going to shift things to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;right align&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there... Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don&amp;#39;t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don&amp;#39;t let anyone else tell you differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty. Yeah... Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;#39;s a wrap, yo! You survived theÂ tumultuousÂ waters of alignment. Image alignment achievement unlocked!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Markup: HTML Tags and Formatting</title>
   <link href="/tests/2013/01/11/2222-markup-html-tags-and-formatting/"/>
   <updated>2013-01-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2013/01/11/2222-markup-html-tags-and-formatting</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Headings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Header one&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Header two&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Header three&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Header four&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Header five&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;Header six&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Single line blockquote:
&lt;blockquote&gt;Stay hungry. Stay foolish.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Multi line blockquote with a cite reference:
&lt;blockquote&gt;People think focus means saying yes to the thing you&amp;#39;ve got to focus on. But that&amp;#39;s not what it means at all. It means saying no to the hundred other good ideas that there are. You have to pick carefully. I&amp;#39;m actually as proud of the things we haven&amp;#39;t done as the things I have done. Innovation is saying no to 1,000 things. &lt;cite&gt;Steve Jobs - Apple Worldwide Developers&amp;#39; Conference, 1997&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;Employee&lt;/th&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;Salary&lt;/th&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://example.org/&quot;&gt;John Doe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;$1&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;Because that&amp;#39;s all Steve Jobs needed for a salary.&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://example.org/&quot;&gt;Jane Doe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;$100K&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;For all the blogging she does.&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://example.org/&quot;&gt;Fred Bloggs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;$100M&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;Pictures are worth a thousand words, right? So Jane x 1,000.&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://example.org/&quot;&gt;Jane Bloggs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;$100B&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;With hair like that?! Enough said...&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Definition Lists&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;Definition List Title&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Definition list division.&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;Startup&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;A startup company or startup is a company or temporary organization designed to search for a repeatable and scalable business model.&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;#dowork&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Coined by Rob Dyrdek and his personal body guard Christopher &amp;quot;Big Black&amp;quot; Boykins, &amp;quot;Do Work&amp;quot; works as a self motivator, to motivating your friends.&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;Do It Live&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;I&amp;#39;ll let Bill O&amp;#39;Reilly will &lt;a title=&quot;We&#39;ll Do It Live&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O_HyZ5aW76c&quot;&gt;explain&lt;/a&gt; this one.&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Unordered Lists (Nested)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item one
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item one
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item one&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ordered List (Nested)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item one
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item one
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item one&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;HTML Tags&lt;/h2&gt;
These supported tags come from the WordPress.com code &lt;a title=&quot;Code&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/code/&quot;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Address Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;address&gt;1 Infinite Loop
Cupertino, CA 95014
United States&lt;/address&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anchor Tag (aka. Link)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an example of a &lt;a title=&quot;Apple&quot; href=&quot;http://apple.com&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abbreviation Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The abbreviation &lt;abbr title=&quot;Seriously&quot;&gt;srsly&lt;/abbr&gt; stands for &amp;quot;seriously&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acronym Tag (&lt;em&gt;deprecated in HTML5&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The acronym &lt;acronym title=&quot;For The Win&quot;&gt;ftw&lt;/acronym&gt; stands for &amp;quot;for the win&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big TagÂ &lt;strong&gt;(&lt;em&gt;deprecated in HTML5&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These tests are a &lt;big&gt;big&lt;/big&gt; deal, but this tag is no longer supported in HTML5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cite Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Code is poetry.&amp;quot; --&lt;cite&gt;Automattic&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Code Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will learn later on in these tests that &lt;code&gt;word-wrap: break-word;&lt;/code&gt; will be your best friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delete Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag will let you &lt;del&gt;strikeout text&lt;/del&gt;, but this tag is no longer supported in HTML5 (use the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;strike&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; instead).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emphasize Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emphasize tag should &lt;em&gt;italicize&lt;/em&gt; text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insert Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag should denote &lt;ins&gt;inserted&lt;/ins&gt; text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keyboard Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This scarsly known tag emulates &lt;kbd&gt;keyboard text&lt;/kbd&gt;, which is usually styled like the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preformatted Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag styles large blocks of code.
&lt;pre&gt;.post-title {
    margin: 0 0 5px;
    font-weight: bold;
    font-size: 38px;
    line-height: 1.2;
    and here&amp;#39;s a line of some really, really, really, really long text, just to see how the PRE tag handles it and to find out how it overflows;
}&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Quote Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;q&gt;Developers, developers, developers...&lt;/q&gt; --Steve Ballmer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strike TagÂ &lt;strong&gt;(&lt;em&gt;deprecated in HTML5&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag shows &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:line-through;&quot;&gt;strike-through text&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strong Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag shows &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;strong&gt; text.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscript Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting our science styling on with H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O, which should push the &amp;quot;2&amp;quot; down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Superscript Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still sticking with science and Isaac Newton&amp;#39;s E = MC&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;, which should lift the 2 up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teletype TagÂ &lt;strong&gt;(&lt;em&gt;deprecated in HTML5&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This rarely used tag emulates &lt;tt&gt;teletype text&lt;/tt&gt;, which is usually styled like the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Variable Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This allows you to denote &lt;var&gt;variables&lt;/var&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Markup: Image Alignment</title>
   <link href="/tests/2013/01/10/2215-markup-image-alignment/"/>
   <updated>2013-01-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2013/01/10/2215-markup-image-alignment</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;Welcome to image alignment! The best way to demonstrate the ebb and flow of the various image positioning options is to nestle them snuggly among an ocean of words. Grab a paddle and let&amp;#39;s get started.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the topic of alignment, it should be noted that users can choose from the options ofÂ &lt;em&gt;None&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Left&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Right, &lt;/em&gt;andÂ &lt;em&gt;Center&lt;/em&gt;. In addition, they also get the options ofÂ &lt;em&gt;Thumbnail&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Medium&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Large&lt;/em&gt;Â &amp;amp;Â &lt;em&gt;Fullsize&lt;/em&gt;.
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-906 aligncenter&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg&quot; width=&quot;580&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
The image above happens to beÂ &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;centered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-904 alignleft&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The rest of this paragraph is fillerÂ for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150x150 image, which is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left aligned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.Â &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one moreÂ sentenceÂ here, we&amp;#39;ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image inÂ seamlessÂ transition. Again, letting the do it&amp;#39;s thang.Â Mission accomplished!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now for a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;massively large image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. It also has &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;alignnone  wp-image-907&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-905 alignright&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now we&amp;#39;re going to shift things to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;right align&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there... Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don&amp;#39;t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don&amp;#39;t let anyone else tell you differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty.Â Yeah... Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And just when you thought we were done, we&amp;#39;re going to do them all over again with captions!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_906&amp;quot; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;580&amp;quot;]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-906  &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg&quot; width=&quot;580&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt; Look at 580x300 getting some &lt;a title=&quot;Image Settings&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/images/image-settings/&quot;&gt;caption&lt;/a&gt; love.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above happens to beÂ &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;centered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. The caption also has a link in it, just to see if it does anything funky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_904&amp;quot; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;150&amp;quot;]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-904  &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt; Itty-bitty caption.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The rest of this paragraph is fillerÂ for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150x150 image, which is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left aligned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.Â &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one moreÂ sentenceÂ here, we&amp;#39;ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image inÂ seamlessÂ transition. Again, letting the do it&amp;#39;s thang. Mission accomplished!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now for a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;massively large image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. It also has &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_907&amp;quot; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;1200&amp;quot;]&lt;img class=&quot; wp-image-907&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt; Massive image comment for your eyeballs.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_905&amp;quot; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;quot;]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-905 &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt; Feels good to be right all the time.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now we&amp;#39;re going to shift things to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;right align&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there... Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don&amp;#39;t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don&amp;#39;t let anyone else tell you differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty. Yeah... Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;#39;s a wrap, yo! You survived theÂ tumultuousÂ waters of alignment. Image alignment achievement unlocked!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Markup: Text Alignment</title>
   <link href="/tests/2013/01/09/1100-markup-text-alignment/"/>
   <updated>2013-01-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2013/01/09/1100-markup-text-alignment</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Default&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a paragraph. It should not have any alignment of any kind. It should just flow like you would normally expect. Nothing fancy. Just straight up text, free flowing, with love. Completely neutral and not picking a side or sitting on the fence. It just is. It just freaking is. It likes where it is. It does not feel compelled to pick a side. Leave him be. It will just be better that way. Trust me.
&lt;h3&gt;Left Align&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:left;&quot;&gt;This is a paragraph. It is left aligned. Because of this, it is a bit more liberal in it&amp;#39;s views. It&amp;#39;s favorite color is green. Left align tends to be more eco-friendly, but it provides no concrete evidence that it really is. Even though it likes share the wealth evenly, it leaves the equal distribution up to justified alignment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Center Align&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;This is a paragraph. It is center aligned. Center is, but nature, a fence sitter. A flip flopper. It has a difficult time making up its mind. It wants to pick a side. Really, it does. It has the best intentions, but it tends to complicate matters more than help. The best you can do is try to win it over and hope for the best. I hear center align does take bribes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Right Align&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:right;&quot;&gt;This is a paragraph. It is right aligned. It is a bit more conservative in it&#39;s views. It&#39;s prefers to not be told what to do or how to do it. Right align totally owns a slew of guns and loves to head to the range for some practice. Which is cool and all. I mean, it&#39;s a pretty good shot from at least four or five football fields away. Dead on. So boss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Justify Align&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:justify;&quot;&gt;This is a paragraph. It is justify aligned. It gets really mad when people associate it with Justin Timberlake. Typically, justified is pretty straight laced. It likes everything to be in it&#39;s place and not all cattywampusÂ like the rest of the aligns. I am not saying that makes it better than the rest of the aligns, but it does tend to put off more of anÂ elitistÂ attitude.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Markup: Title With Markup</title>
   <link href="/tests/2013/01/05/1200-markup-title-with-markup/"/>
   <updated>2013-01-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2013/01/05/1200-markup-title-with-markup</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Verify that:
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;The post title renders the word &amp;quot;with&amp;quot; in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;italics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt; and the word &amp;quot;markup&amp;quot; in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;The post title markup should be removed from the browser window / tab.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The New York Times: Polk Award for Silver</title>
   <link href="/media/2012/04/05/polk-award/"/>
   <updated>2012-04-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2012/04/05/polk-award</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three Bloomberg News reporters — Ben Elgin, Alan Katz and Vernon Silver — won the international reporting award for articles about Western companies that sell surveillance technology and equipment to repressive governments for use against opposition figures. Their stories showed how telephone transcripts generated by German computers had led to the arrest and torture of a human rights activist in Bahrain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2012/02/20/nyregion/anthony-shadid-times-correspondent-posthumously-honored.html&quot;&gt;Polk Award for International Reporting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Template: Featured Image (Vertical)</title>
   <link href="/tests/2012/03/15/1836-template-featured-image-vertical/"/>
   <updated>2012-03-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2012/03/15/1836-template-featured-image-vertical</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This post should display aÂ &lt;a title=&quot;Featured Images&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/featured-images/#setting-a-featured-image&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;featured image&lt;/a&gt;, if the themeÂ &lt;a title=&quot;Post Thumbnails&quot; href=&quot;http://codex.wordpress.org/Post_Thumbnails&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;supports it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non-square images can provide some unique styling issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post tests a vertical featured image.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Template: Featured Image (Horizontal)</title>
   <link href="/tests/2012/03/15/1815-template-featured-image-horizontal/"/>
   <updated>2012-03-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2012/03/15/1815-template-featured-image-horizontal</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This post should display a &lt;a title=&quot;Featured Images&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/featured-images/#setting-a-featured-image&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;featured image&lt;/a&gt;, if the theme &lt;a title=&quot;Post Thumbnails&quot; href=&quot;http://codex.wordpress.org/Post_Thumbnails&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;supports it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non-square images can provide some unique styling issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post tests a horizontal featured image.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Template: More Tag</title>
   <link href="/tests/2012/03/15/1741-template-more-tag/"/>
   <updated>2012-03-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2012/03/15/1741-template-more-tag</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This content is before the &lt;a title=&quot;The More Tag&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/splitting-content/more-tag/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;more tag&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right after thisÂ sentenceÂ should be a &amp;quot;continue reading&amp;quot; button of some sort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this content is after the more tag.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Bob Hecht, Euphronios Dealer, Dies at 92</title>
   <link href="/news/2012/02/11/bob-hecht-euphronios-dealer-dies-at-92/"/>
   <updated>2012-02-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2012/02/11/bob-hecht-euphronios-dealer-dies-at-92</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/Robert_Hecht.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hecht in Rome&quot;&gt;
Hecht in Rome&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob Hecht, the American art dealer who brought the world the finest vases by the greatest Greek vase painter (and spawned the globetrotting tales of intrigue behind them) died in Paris this week. His death comes less than a month after his trial in Rome came to an end when the statute of limitations ran out on charges related to the Euphronios krater and other artifacts. His lifelong adventure ended with a clean criminal record and his most famous vases back on Italian soil. Until the finish, he had a twinkle in his eye, and I thank him for sharing what he could about his incredible life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2012/02/10/arts/design/robert-hecht-antiquities-dealer-dies-at-92.html&quot;&gt;NYT: Bob Hecht, 92&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Lost Chalice Found—and Fixed</title>
   <link href="/news/2010/12/31/lost-chalice/"/>
   <updated>2010-12-31T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2010/12/31/lost-chalice</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/KylixVillaGiulia.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Once shattered, on display for first time in 20 years&quot;&gt;
Once shattered, on display for first time in 20 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The oldest known vase by the Leonardo da Vinci of ancient Greece has emerged from hiding after two decades. Last seen in public at a June 1990 auction at Sotheby’s in New York, Euphronios’ Sarpedon kylix has gone on display at Rome’s Villa Giulia museum with no fanfare or public announcement. Making the appearance more significant, the cup has been repaired—fixing the damage done when a Swiss police officer dropped it during an inventory of antiquities seized from dealer Giacomo Medici at the Geneva Freeport in 1995. The “lost chalice” now shares a glass case with a handful of other vases in a room dedicated to artifacts returned to Italy by American museums and collectors. Its label, which has no accession number, describes it as coming from the Geneva raid (and doesn’t mention that, technically, it’s still Medici’s property, pending the resolution of his legal cases).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cup is in good company: the case next to it holds another rare, signed Euphronios, a fragmentary krater depicting Athena that was sold at the same auction and later given to Italy by collector Shelby White. The repaired kylix has been on display since at least May (when I first spotted it there) and I’ve been waiting to see if there’d be any announcement before posting on it. As this is the biggest development in Greek pots for 2010, New Year’s Eve seemed like a good time. What remains to be seen is if it will ever get displayed alongside its bigger twin, the Met’s former “Euphronios Krater.” That vase, which depicts the same scene, is also at Villa Giulia, in a separate wing.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>True Trial Ends</title>
   <link href="/news/2010/10/16/true-trial-ends/"/>
   <updated>2010-10-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2010/10/16/true-trial-ends</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Rome trial of former Getty antiquities chief Marion True fizzled out after five years when the statute of limitations ran out on the charges. True, who denied the allegations that she’d played a role in stocking the California museum with artifacts looted from Italy, never got to present her defense. It’s just a matter of months before the clock also runs out on charges against her co-defendant, Bob Hecht, who is accused of dealing in loot including the Euphronios krater, and also says he’s innocent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2010/10/14/arts/design/14true.html?ref=marion_true&quot;&gt;NYT: True’s Rome Trial Ends&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>True: “greatest contempt” for Getty</title>
   <link href="/news/2010/10/16/true-greatest-conte/"/>
   <updated>2010-10-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2010/10/16/true-greatest-conte</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Former Getty curator Marion True finally gets her well-deserved say now that her Rome trial is over. In a stunning interview by Hugh Eakin (published on The New Yorker’s Web site) True tells off both the Italians (who had charged her in dealing with loot) and the Getty (which had been paying her legal bills). “My greatest sadness is that the Italians were able to intimidate the entire American art world, and especially museums, without having to produce any evidence at all,” she says. Of the Getty, which she essentially says hung her out to dry: “I have nothing but the greatest contempt for them in the world.”
New Yorker: True Speaks Out&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Clearing Floats</title>
   <link href="/tests/2010/08/01/1242-clearing-floats/"/>
   <updated>2010-08-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2010/08/01/1242-clearing-floats</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The last item in this page&amp;#39;s content is a floated image. Make sure any elements after it are clearing properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;alignleft size-thumbnail wp-image-827&quot; title=&quot;Camera&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2010/08/manhattansummer.jpg?w=150&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;112&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Post Format: Video (YouTube)</title>
   <link href="/tests/2010/06/02/0500-post-format-video-youtube/"/>
   <updated>2010-06-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2010/06/02/0500-post-format-video-youtube</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nwe-H6l4beM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The official music video of &amp;quot;Rise Up&amp;quot; from &lt;a title=&quot;Eddy Music&quot; href=&quot;http://eddymusic.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eddy&amp;#39;s&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title=&quot;Eddy - Start An Uproar! EP&quot; href=&quot;http://bit.ly/bVmAyI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Start An Uproar!&lt;/a&gt; EP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about &lt;a title=&quot;WordPress Embeds&quot; href=&quot;http://codex.wordpress.org/Embeds&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;WordPress Embeds&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Post Format: Aside</title>
   <link href="/tests/2010/05/09/1051-post-format-aside/"/>
   <updated>2010-05-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2010/05/09/1051-post-format-aside</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I never tried to prove nothing, just wanted to give a good show. My life has always been my music, it&amp;#39;s always come first, but the music ain&amp;#39;t worth nothing if you can&amp;#39;t lay it on the public. The main thing is to live for that audience, &amp;#39;cause what you&amp;#39;re there for is to please the people.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>An Etruscan Lord Elgin</title>
   <link href="/news/2010/05/08/an-etruscan-lord-elgin/"/>
   <updated>2010-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2010/05/08/an-etruscan-lord-elgin</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In a compelling twist, Michael Kimmelman shows how Italy winning back the Krater makes a good argument for the British Museum keeping the Parthenon Marbles: 
Stolen property is stolen property. But how curious that an ancient Greek vase, which centuries after it was made came into the possession of an Etruscan collector (a kind of ancient Elgin) living on what is now the outskirts of Rome, and then ended up buried for thousands of years below what became modern Italy, is today Italian cultural patrimony. By that definition, Elgin’s loot is arguably British patrimony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2010/05/09/arts/09abroad.html?pagewanted=all&quot;&gt;NYT: Culture’s Borders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Post Format: Status</title>
   <link href="/tests/2010/04/04/1121-post-format-status/"/>
   <updated>2010-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2010/04/04/1121-post-format-status</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;WordPress, how do I love thee? Let me count the ways (in 140 characters or less).&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Post Format: Link</title>
   <link href="/tests/2010/03/07/1006-post-format-link/"/>
   <updated>2010-03-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2010/03/07/1006-post-format-link</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://make.wordpress.org/themes&quot; title=&quot;The WordPress Theme Review Team Website&quot;&gt;The WordPress Theme Review Team Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Post Format: Quote</title>
   <link href="/tests/2010/02/05/1013-post-format-quote/"/>
   <updated>2010-02-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2010/02/05/1013-post-format-quote</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;Only one thing is impossible for God: To find any sense in any copyright law on the planet.
&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.brainyquote.com/quotes/quotes/m/marktwain163473.html&quot;&gt;Mark Twain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Troy’s Gold and Bob Hecht</title>
   <link href="/news/2010/01/31/troys-gold-and-bob-hecht/"/>
   <updated>2010-01-31T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2010/01/31/troys-gold-and-bob-hecht</id>
   <content type="html">![Hecht in Rome](/assets/img/Robert_Hecht.jpg)

Hecht in Rome

A feature in the Philadelphia Inquirer revives the mystery of the Penn Museum’s gold—whether it came from Troy, and how it got to America—and in the process reveals that the dealer behind the sale was the very same man who brought the Euphronios krater to the Metropolitan Museum of Art: Bob Hecht.

“Hecht confirmed that he was indeed the source of Penn’s Trojan-style gold, with Allen acting as his agent. Hecht easily recalled the pieces and proclaimed them “beautiful.” He said he had purchased them from another dealer, George Zakos, who is dead… He said Zakos, who lived in Switzerland, had not shared the objects’ history. ‘He didn’t say, and I didn’t ask,’ Hecht said. ‘I thought it was beautiful, and I thought it was genuine.’”

[Tracing the Gold](http://www.philly.com/philly/news/homepage/20100131_Tracing_ancient_roots_of_Penn_Museum_s_gold.html?viewAll=y)</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Post Format: Chat</title>
   <link href="/tests/2010/01/08/0959-post-format-chat/"/>
   <updated>2010-01-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2010/01/08/0959-post-format-chat</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Strange as it may seem, they give ball players nowadays very peculiar names.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Funny names?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Nicknames, nicknames. Now, on the St. Louis team we have Who&amp;#39;s on first, What&amp;#39;s on second, I Don&amp;#39;t Know is on third--&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: That&amp;#39;s what I want to find out. I want you to tell me the names of the fellows on the St. Louis team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: I&amp;#39;m telling you. Who&amp;#39;s on first, What&amp;#39;s on second, I Don&amp;#39;t Know is on third--&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: You know the fellows&amp;#39; names?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Well, then who&amp;#39;s playing first?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: I mean the fellow&amp;#39;s name on first base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Who.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: The fellow playin&amp;#39; first base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Who.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: The guy on first base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Who is on first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Well, what are you askin&amp;#39; me for?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: I&amp;#39;m not asking you--I&amp;#39;m telling you. Who is on first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: I&amp;#39;m asking you--who&amp;#39;s on first?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: That&amp;#39;s the man&amp;#39;s name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: That&amp;#39;s who&amp;#39;s name?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: When you pay off the first baseman every month, who gets the money?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Every dollar of it. And why not, the man&amp;#39;s entitled to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Who is?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: So who gets it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Why shouldn&amp;#39;t he? Sometimes his wife comes down and collects it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Who&amp;#39;s wife?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Yes. After all, the man earns it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Who does?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Absolutely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Well, all I&amp;#39;m trying to find out is what&amp;#39;s the guy&amp;#39;s name on first base?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Oh, no, no. What is on second base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: I&amp;#39;m not asking you who&amp;#39;s on second.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Who&amp;#39;s on first!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: St. Louis has a good outfield?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Oh, absolutely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: The left fielder&amp;#39;s name?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: I don&amp;#39;t know, I just thought I&amp;#39;d ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Well, I just thought I&amp;#39;d tell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Then tell me who&amp;#39;s playing left field?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Who&amp;#39;s playing first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Stay out of the infield! The left fielder&amp;#39;s name?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Because.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Oh, he&amp;#39;s center field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Wait a minute. You got a pitcher on this team?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Wouldn&amp;#39;t this be a fine team without a pitcher?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Tell me the pitcher&amp;#39;s name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Now, when the guy at bat bunts the ball--me being a good catcher--I want to throw the guy out at first base, so I pick up the ball and throw it to who?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Now, that&amp;#39;s he first thing you&amp;#39;ve said right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: I DON&amp;#39;T EVEN KNOW WHAT I&amp;#39;M TALKING ABOUT!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Don&amp;#39;t get excited. Take it easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: I throw the ball to first base, whoever it is grabs the ball, so the guy runs to second. Who picks up the ball and throws it to what. What throws it to I don&amp;#39;t know. I don&amp;#39;t know throws it back to tomorrow--a triple play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Yeah, it could be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Another guy gets up and it&amp;#39;s a long ball to center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Because.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: Why? I don&amp;#39;t know. And I don&amp;#39;t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: What was that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Costello: I said, I DON&amp;#39;T CARE!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott: Oh, that&amp;#39;s our shortstop!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Thomas Hoving, Met Chief and Journalist, Dies</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/12/10/thomas-hoving-dies-at-78/"/>
   <updated>2009-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/12/10/thomas-hoving-dies-at-78</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/popup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Thomas Hoving (NYT)&quot;&gt;
Thomas Hoving (NYT)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thomas Hoving, the former Met director who brought us King Tut and the Euphronios krater, has died. He was 78. Hoving loved an adventure. And he made the mummies dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2009/12/11/arts/design/11hoving.html&quot;&gt;NYT: Hoving, Who Shook Up the Met, Dies at 78&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Met’s von Bothmer Dies at 90</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/10/17/mets-von-bothmer-dies-at-90/"/>
   <updated>2009-10-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/10/17/mets-von-bothmer-dies-at-90</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/botmerspan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dietrich von Bothmer&quot;&gt;
Dietrich von Bothmer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An era in the study and collecting of Greek vases has come to an end with the death of Dietrich von Bothmer, whose modern career became intertwined with the ancient work of the artist Euphronios. From the first Euphronios he saw (in Berlin), which inspired his vocation, to the famous krater he helped the Metropolitan Museum of Art buy in 1972, to the one that got away—the krater’s smaller twin chalice, which he twice tried to acquire (in 1973 and 1990)—Dietrich von Bothmer’s biography became inseparable from that of the Athenian master and his pottery. While a chapter has come to a close, neither man’s story is over. The documents, photos and vase fragments he’s left behind in his files (NYT photo, above) and other archives may allow the curator and professor to keep illuminating the world of ancient art, even after his passing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2009/10/15/arts/15bothmer.html&quot;&gt;NYT: Dietrich von Bothmer, Curator and Art Historian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Wall Street Journal: A Celebrity in Low-Key Digs</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/10/01/wall-street-journal-a-celebrity-in-low-key-digs/"/>
   <updated>2009-10-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/10/01/wall-street-journal-a-celebrity-in-low-key-digs</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Silver, chronicler of the criminals, curators, detectives and politicians who have chased after the bowl in recent decades, insists that their story too is now an essential part of the krater’s significance, and thus an important element in the way the museum should present it. “Objects accrue meanings over time,” he says. “People may go to jail today because of this 2,500-year-old pot. Reputations have been won and lost because of it. To label it as just a work of art would be a mistake.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052970203863204574345011111945666.html&quot;&gt;WSJ on The Lost Chalice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Lost Chalice: SmartMoney’s 5 Smart Books</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/10/01/smart-moneys-5-smart-books/"/>
   <updated>2009-10-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/10/01/smart-moneys-5-smart-books</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Lost Chalice&lt;/em&gt; is the fascinating story of how a band of grave robbers turned up two priceless ancient works of art — and how these ill-gotten masterpieces made their way to Sotheby’s, to private collections and to the Metropolitan Museum of Art. Silver shows how the illicit trade of stolen antiquities implicates the art world’s most prestigious institutions. He takes us alongside detectives and reporters who doggedly pursue elusive treasures across decades and continents, chasing leads to Switzerland, Beirut…and Malibu. Millions are made while laws — and irreplaceable artworks — are broken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.smartmoney.com/Spending/Deals/5-Smart-Books-Our-Staffs-Latest-Picks/&quot;&gt;SmartMoney on The Lost Chalice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Met Curator Fills Gaps on Museum “Rogues”</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/10/01/mets-o/"/>
   <updated>2009-10-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/10/01/mets-o</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/MuscarellaPhoto.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oscar White Muscarella&quot;&gt;
Oscar White Muscarella&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Curator Oscar White Muscarella, the longtime in-house critic of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, reviews a new book on the Met as a starting point to dredge up a few decades of alleged misdeeds and “clandestine acts.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.scoop.co.nz/stories/HL0909/S00139.htm&quot;&gt;Muscarella: The Met/Rogues’ Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>NPR: Italy Cracks Down on Raiders of Lost Art</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/08/16/npr-italy-cracks-down-on-raiders-of-lost-art/"/>
   <updated>2009-08-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/08/16/npr-italy-cracks-down-on-raiders-of-lost-art</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;NPR’s Sylvia Poggioli reports: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The expert who helped nail down the exact spot where the pot was found is Vernon Silver, an American journalist with a degree in archaeology from Oxford. His new book, The Lost Chalice, traces the story of the looted vase’s travels from a tomb in Italy to Switzerland to New York and back to Italy through the labyrinthine world of smugglers and shady dealers in an illicit trade that fed a network of American collectors and institutions.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;embed src=&quot;http://www.npr.org/v2/?i=111734951&amp;#38;m=111748597&amp;#38;t=audio&quot; height=&quot;386&quot; wmode=&quot;opaque&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; base=&quot;http://www.npr.org&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot;&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=111734951&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;NPR: Italy Cracks Down on Raiders of Lost Art&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Edge Case: No Content</title>
   <link href="/tests/2009/08/06/1239-edge-case-no-content/"/>
   <updated>2009-08-06T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2009/08/06/1239-edge-case-no-content</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Providence Journal: “Vernon Silver’s fascinating account”</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/07/18/providence-journal-vernon-silvers-fascinating-account/"/>
   <updated>2009-07-18T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/07/18/providence-journal-vernon-silvers-fascinating-account</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...a world of incredible secrecy, where art rises into view only to disappear for decades, where sales are anonymous, museum officials turn blind eyes, and where beauty is measured in dollars and euros.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.projo.com/books/content/BOOK-LOST-CHALICE_07-12-09_NUEQOTP_v12.f78b7b.html&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;ProJo: The Lost Chalice&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Medici Off The Hook For Krater?</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/07/18/medici-off-the-hook-for-krater/"/>
   <updated>2009-07-18T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/07/18/medici-off-the-hook-for-krater</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;While the Rome appeals court affirmed Giacomo Medici’s conviction for antiquities trafficking, it absolved him on charges of handling objects that ended up at the Met—on what appears to be a procedural technicality. Only the full, written sentence, expected within three months, will explain what this means for the Euphronios krater.
Bloomberg: Rome Court Upholds Medici Conviction&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The New York Times on “The Lost Chalice”</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/07/07/the-new-york-times-on-the-lost-chalice/"/>
   <updated>2009-07-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/07/07/the-new-york-times-on-the-lost-chalice</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/abroad2_650.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Vernon at the tomb&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Vernon at the tomb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York Times’ Michael Kimmelman has published a terrific feature on “The Lost Chalice” and the road trip we took the other day to the overgrown Etruscan countryside. First we tromped around the long-sought site of the clandestine dig that four decades ago uncovered some of the world’s finest ancient art. Then I introduced him to a key character from “The Lost Chalice,” the last known surviving member of the tomb-robbing team that unearthed the haul. And on the way back into Rome we stopped to see the biggest prize from the illicit excavation—the Euphronios krater— itself in a new context at the Villa Giulia museum, far from its former home in New York’s Met.
Stolen Beauty: A Greek Urn’s Underworld&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The New York Times: A Greek Urn’s Underworld</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/07/07/the-new-york-times-a-greek-urns-underworld/"/>
   <updated>2009-07-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/07/07/the-new-york-times-a-greek-urns-underworld</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“The Lost Chalice: The Epic Hunt for a Priceless Masterpiece,” just published by William Morrow, makes a first-class page turner out of the stolen krater’s travels from ancient Greece to Etruscan Italy to New York and then back here — and of the travails of another work also by the sublime Euphronios, a kylix, or chalice, which was looted from the same spot here in Cerveteri, a town northwest of Rome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vernon Silver, a 40-year-old American journalist and a doctoral student in archaeology at Oxford, wrote the book. “This is the whole illicit antiquities trade writ small,” he said a few days ago. “The two works started out in the hands of the same Greek artist, 2,500 years ago, ended up going through the same shady Italian dealer by different routes to America, one the public route, the other underground, and both end up back here in Italy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tale is one neither Met officials nor Italian authorities will be pleased to find so conscientiously recounted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2009/07/08/arts/design/08abroad.html?ref=design&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Stolen Beauty: A Greek Urn’s Underworld&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>“The Lost Chalice” on MarketWatch with Jon Friedman</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/07/06/the-lost-chalice-on-marketwatch-with-jon-friedman/"/>
   <updated>2009-07-06T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/07/06/the-lost-chalice-on-marketwatch-with-jon-friedman</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; width=&quot;512&quot; height=&quot;288&quot; src=&quot;http://live.wsj.com/public/page/embed-646C1CD8_73A7_45E6_9A52_FCF993DE9C2B.html&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Edge Case: Many Categories</title>
   <link href="/tests/2009/07/02/0500-edge-case-many-categories/"/>
   <updated>2009-07-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2009/07/02/0500-edge-case-many-categories</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This post has many categories.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Exhibitionists: “Rogues’ Gallery” Reviewed</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/06/27/exhibitionists-rogues-gallery-reviewed/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/06/27/exhibitionists-rogues-gallery-reviewed</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Michael Gross’ new book on the Met, “Rogues’ Gallery,” touches on the Euphronios episode and some of the characters behind it. It’s reviewed in The New York Times this Sunday.
Exhibitionists&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How eBay Fakes May Be Saving Tombs</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/06/24/how-ebay-fakes-may-be-saving-tombs/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/06/24/how-ebay-fakes-may-be-saving-tombs</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The New York Times takes a look at the role fakes (and their sale online) may have in reducing illicit excavation of genuine antiquities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ideas.blogs.nytimes.com/2009/06/24/how-fakes-on-ebay-save-antiquities/&quot;&gt;Idea of the Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hoving Takes On The Getty</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/06/17/hoving-takes-on-the-getty/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/06/17/hoving-takes-on-the-getty</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Thomas Hoving, the former Met director, has been publishing his memoirs online. A recent chapter takes on fakes, fraud and repatriation from some big museums.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.artnet.com/magazineus/features/hoving/artful-tom-chapter-thirty-one6-12-09.asp&quot;&gt;Artful Tom: The Getty Wars&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Euphronios Krater’s New Home</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/06/09/t/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/06/09/t</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/KraterVillaGiulia.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Sarpedon in Rome&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Sarpedon in Rome&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sarpedon krater by Euphronios went on display a few weeks ago at its new permanent (until further notice) home at Rome’s Villa Giulia museum. The Metropolitan Museum of Art returned the krater to Italy in January 2008.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Behind the krater is the huge kylix potted by Euphronios and painted by Onesimos—the one the J. Paul Getty Museum surrendered to Italy in 1999, prompting Roman art dealer Giacomo Medici to hand over three fragments from the cup. The fragments, which haven’t been glued into the previously restored kylix, are also in the display case.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Krater Pulled From Auction in New York</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/06/04/krater-pulled-from-auction-in-new-york/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/06/04/krater-pulled-from-auction-in-new-york</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;U.S. Customs says a krater got yanked from auction in New York, in part because of its possible link to a certain Roman art dealer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The investigation into the Corinthian column krater revealed it may have been illegally introduced into the art market by Giacomo Medici and a third party at Sotheby’s Auction house in 1985.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ice.gov/pi/nr/0906/090601newyork.htm&quot;&gt;ICE Press Release&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Thomas Hoving, former director of the Metropolitan Museum of Art</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/06/01/thomas-hoving-former-director-of-the-metropolitan-museum-of-art/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/06/01/thomas-hoving-former-director-of-the-metropolitan-museum-of-art</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In his brilliant The Lost Chalice Vernon Silver has gone far beyond merely slicing open the Gordion knot obscuring the world-famous ancient Greek chalices made by Euphronios, the Leonardo of the 6th century BC, he has patiently untied that knot in a spine-tingling read.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Daily Beast: “The Tomb Robbers”</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/06/01/the-tomb-robbers/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/06/01/the-tomb-robbers</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the trail of a looted chalice, Vernon Silver exposes the dark side of the antiquities trade, from tomb robbers in Italy to museum curators in New York and Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For anyone who has ever stood under the halogen lights of a museum and wondered just where, exactly, an Etruscan artifact is from, Vernon Silver has the answer, which may involve tomb raiders, smugglers, unscrupulous art dealers, and willfully blind museum curators. A Rome-based correspondent for Bloomberg who is also an Oxford-trained archeologist, Silver, in his new book, The Lost Chalice, describes the seedy underworld of the antiquities trade in such vivid detail that one can almost smell the fresh earth of a pillaged archeological site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unbridled looting of Italy’s buried treasures before 1970 is one of this country’s darkest cultural chapters. Thousands of valuable artifacts were fished from the soil and sold to art dealers, who passed them on to private collectors and major museums. A 1970 Unesco convention on cultural heritage exposed the illicit practice and established procedures for repatriating stolen goods. Countries trying to reclaim their antiquities from museums around the world have better luck with those acquired after the 1970 accord. Those acquired before the pact generally stay on the museum shelves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thedailybeast.com/blogs-and-stories/2009-05-30/the-tomb-robbers/full/&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;The Tomb Robbers&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Lost Chalice Released Today</title>
   <link href="/news/2009/06/01/the-lost-chalice-released-today/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/news/2009/06/01/the-lost-chalice-released-today</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Lost Chalice&lt;/em&gt; is out. Enjoy, and thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Sharon Waxman, author of Loot</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/06/01/sharon-waxman-author-of-loot/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/06/01/sharon-waxman-author-of-loot</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Setting up his tale as a mystery to be solved Silver takes a micro approach to a great big problem, that of looted antiquities in modern times... a welcome glimpse into the modern, secret journey of such ancient objects.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://sharonwaxman.typepad.com/loot/2009/04/vernon-silver-takes-on-giacomo-medici-.html&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Sharon Waxman, author of Loot on The Lost Chalice&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Kirkus Reviews</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/06/01/kirkus-reviews/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/06/01/kirkus-reviews</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“Vernon&amp;#39;s sharply rendered account is engrossing. A densely packed, dizzyingly detailed tale of art and espionage.”&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>James L. Swanson, author of Manhunt</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/06/01/james-l-swanson-author-of-manhunt/"/>
   <updated>2009-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/06/01/james-l-swanson-author-of-manhunt</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vernon Silver has written an utterly compelling, page-turner of a book. The Lost Chalice is a riveting story of tomb robbers and antiquities smugglers, high-stakes auctioneers and the princely chiefs of the world’s most prestigious museums—all vying to get their hands on an ancient masterpiece. It’s a terrific read, from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Publishers Weekly</title>
   <link href="/media/2009/05/31/publishers-weekly/"/>
   <updated>2009-05-31T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/media/2009/05/31/publishers-weekly</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“A captivating tale of ancient art as a modern hot commodity... Silver’s telling is infused with an infectious curiosity about the illicit art trade and an equally infectious appreciation of the art itself. ”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.publishersweekly.com/article/CA6660208.html?industryid=47263&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Publishers Weekly&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Edge Case: Nested And Mixed Lists</title>
   <link href="/tests/2009/05/15/1748-edge-case-nested-and-mixed-lists/"/>
   <updated>2009-05-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/tests/2009/05/15/1748-edge-case-nested-and-mixed-lists</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Nested and mixed lists are an interesting beast. It&amp;#39;s a corner case to make sure that
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;Lists within lists do not break the ordered list numbering order&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;Your list styles go deep enough.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ordered - Unordered - Ordered&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;unordered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;unordered&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ordered - Unordered - Unordered&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;unordered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;unordered&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Unordered - Ordered - Unordered&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;ordered
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Unordered - Unordered - Ordered&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ordered item&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ordered item&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;unordered item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
